forumbacklink.info 2010-05-02

# Free Web Directory - 100% Free Links - Contact Us and Privacy

Full Name: |    
  
Email Address: |    
  
Contact Reason: |   
Message: |    
  
  |   
  
Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

Our Commitment To Privacy

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use your personal information in connection with our  
advertising, content, e-commerce, promotional and service programs and other business activities (the "Program") and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services and the sites of our advertisers.

What Information We Collect

When you visit our site we may collect two types of information: (a) personal information you actively choose to disclose and (b) information  
about you that is collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties in a way not visible to you.(a) Information you actively choose to provide. By choosing to participate in our Program, you must become a Member by disclosing the following  
information, such as: your email address, name, address, phone number and birth date. During the process of registering on our site, participating in various offers, completing surveys, or sending us emails or correspondence, we collect additional information that you may disclose, including for example mobile telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), credit information, social security number, health information and personal preferences regarding lifestyle, products or services.

(b) Passive information collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties. We collect some information about you simply by virtue of you connecting to our web site. Our servers automatically identify your computer by its internet protocol ("IP") address, a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. In addition, to participate in our program you must allow cookies to be active on your system. Cookies are a feature of web browser software (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc.) that allows web servers to recognize which computer is used to access a web site. Cookies simplify subsequent interactions on our site and streamline your transactions on related web pages. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visits, the site pages you viewed, the time spent at each page, and the web sites you visited just before and just after our site. You can disable the cookie function by following the instructions in the "help" section of your browser. However, doing so will likely make it impossible for our system to properly recognize you when you visit our sites, and consequently may make your participation in our program more difficult or impossible. In addition to the information you provide or that is collected automatically from our system, we may obtain information about you from our marketing partners or other third parties, and we combine that information with the information you actively provide or that is automatically collected by our servers.

The term "Information" is used in this policy to refer to both types of information described above, as well as any Information that you provide to  
us directly by phone (including any phone number displayed via caller ID), text or SMS message, U.S. mail or through any other written or oral  
communication with us.

How We Use And Share The Information Collected

We use your Information to administer our business activities, provide customer services such as technical support, distribute information about  
changes to our site, and send you, and enable others to send you, information about products and services that may be of interest to you and  
to contact you or use your Information for any other purpose. We send communications to you ourselves, and your Information also is shared with other organizations that may contact you for any purpose by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication.

OPT-IN NOTICE: By Participating, You Expressly "Opt In" To Receive Information And Grant Us Permission To Share Your Information

By signing up for our Program you expressly opt in to receive future information about products and services from us and from a variety of  
advertisers to whom we may provide your Information. We will share your personal information with third parties, including our advertisers, for any reason we choose, including without limitation for the following purposes: (1) to operate our Program (including the transfer of the information to advertisers or to third parties who maintain on our behalf a list of persons having registered with our Program), (2) to permit advertisers or other third parties to use your Information for any purpose such as contacting you by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication for any purpose, (3) to confirm you have completed all of the necessary steps to receive your gift, and (4) as we are required to do by law, including to notify the IRS that you received your gift. As a result, we will transfer your Information to third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control.In addition, in the event we consider a transaction involving the purchase  
or sale of our assets or stock, other companies may review our records, including your Information, to make business decisions about the  
transaction. Likewise, your Information may be transferred to third parties in the event of the sale or acquisition of our company or any of its assets. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant banks, our internet service provider, etc.) also may have access to your information in performing their services.

Special Note About Information You Provide Directly To Our Advertisers.

You are able to access certain advertiser's sites through our site. When you opt to receive information or sign up for an offer from an advertiser, you may be doing so through third party sites and with other companies over which we have no control. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you wish to opt out of those advertisers' mailings, you must do so directly with such advertisers or as otherwise provided on or through their sites.

Security Of Your Information.

We use reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Information. However,  
nearly all Internet transmissions pass through many servers not controlled by us, and therefore we cannot guarantee that any information you provide us or we collect will not be intercepted or altered in that process. Also, as noted above, your Information is shared with third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control.How You Can Choose To "Opt Out" Of Receiving Further Information About  
Products Or Services

If at any time you do not wish to receive further information about products or services from us and wish us to cease providing your Information to third parties, you may chose to "opt-out" through the Unsubscribe/"Opt-Out" page of our site.

Or by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in our newsletter emails.

We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to ten (10) business days from our receipt of your request for the change to be fully effective. If you late give us a clear statement that you want to receive emails from us or our advertisers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request. If we have already provided your email address or other information to an advertiser or other third party before we receive your opt-out request, we cannot prevent them from sending or continuing to send you information or emails and you will need to contact such third party  
directly.

How To Correct, Delete Or Access Your Information

If you wish to access, delete or correct the information you have provided to us through this site, please contact us through the Contact Us section of our site.

Special Rights For Residents Of Certain States

If you are a California resident or another state with specific laws relating to the collection and use of Information, you may have specific  
rights not set forth in this policy. For example, California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party  
company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name registration (email address), the site name you visited and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please request our mailing address buy using the contact us page on this website.

PLEASE CHECK THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES AS WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. SUCH REVISIONS TO THE PRIVACY POLICY SHALL TAKE EFFECT WHEN POSTED. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR SERVICES THROUGH ANY COMMUNICATION CHANNEL FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES. 

FTC DISCLAIMER:

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) issued new rules that go into effect on December 1, 2009. Although we have always operated this site in a way that ensures the highest standards, we always strive to maintain full compliance.

**Reviews/endorsements** :

While we attempt to review information placed on this site to ensure that it meets our "family friendly" guidelines, this process is not perfect. We do not endorse any information or make any claims as to the benefits of any product or item on this site. We do not make any claims to the benefits of advertising through this site, or to the benefits of paying for a featured link on this site.

**Advertising** :

We do not endorse any paid advertisements or featured links on this site or server. All paid placements are clearly not endorsed and our advertising guidelines stipulate that no advertising will be accepted which implies endorsement from us.

**Affiliated products/services** :

This site is able to operate from revenue which comes from product sales and affiliate referral commissions. Outside of featured links and advertisements, no affiliated or advertised products are sold or endorsed directly on this site, and any claims made by such affiliates or advertisers are contained on those outside sites. We are not responsible for any claims made directly by advertisers, affiliates, featured links, or regular links. In the cases where advertisers or affiliates are allowed to publish content on this site, it is clearly stated and clear for any visitor to see that the content has no relation with any endorsements which the operators of this site may or may not make.

In other cases, we may publish or re-publish reviews made by site visitors or contributors to this site, and in those cases we do not claim endorsement, nor are we obligated to monitor or censure such reviews whether they are positive or negative.

**Testimonials** :

We do not claim any endorsement, nor are we obligate to monitor or censure any information uploaded by users to this website. Any claims about a specific hyperlink or website are considered to be from the perspective of the individual or organization that has uploaded it. We do not verify, certify, or endorse any specific item or action suggested, and any individual or organization submitting a link as well as uploading information is to take full responsibility for the information placed. 

**Disclaimer of Endorsement**

The documents, information, and links posted on this server contain text and hypertext links or pointers to information created and maintained by public and private organizations and individuals. These links and pointers are provided for the users convenience. This website does not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, legality, or completeness of this outside information. Further, the inclusion of links or pointers to particular items is neither intended to reflect their importance nor endorse any views expressed, or products or services offered, on these outside sites, or the organizations sponsoring the sites.

All information contained within this website and on this server is deemed to be purely for entertainment purposes only.

If you have any questions or concerns about this disclaimer and our review policies, please do not hesitate to contact us at via the contact form on this page.

PLEASE CHECK THIS DISCLAIMER PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES AS WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS DISCLAIMER. SUCH REVISIONS TO THE DISCLAIMER SHALL TAKE EFFECT WHEN POSTED. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR SERVICES THROUGH ANY COMMUNICATION CHANNEL FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THE DISCLAIMER CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES.
